ACWA Photographs 5743 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Monas, David (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Monat, Peter (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Murphy, James (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Musch, August (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Myers, Evelyn (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Napolitano, Frank (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Negro, Rocco (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Nemser, Hyman (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Ninno, Pat (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Nisselson, Michael (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Nocella, Sam [folder 1 of 3] (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Nocella, Sam [folder 2 of 3] (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Nocella, Sam [folder 3 of 3] (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Norwitch, Harry (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Nuttall, Alfred (Box 9, Folder 7)
- OGrady, Jane (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Oliva, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Oswaldo, Eusepi (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Panick, Frank (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Panken, Judge Jacob (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Pappas, Costas (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Parenti, Patsy (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Patti, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Payne, Ruth V. (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Pecoraro, Ralph J. (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Peel, Elbert (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Penn, Jane (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Peppercorn, B. (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Peppercorn, Max (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Peta, Thomas (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Peterson, Esther [folder 1 of 3] (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Peterson, Esther [folder 2 of 3] (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Peterson, Esther [folder 3 of 3] (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Petito, Robert (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Piepenhagen, A.G. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  See also Box 56, ff7
- Polk, Leo (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Pollack, Jack (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Posner, Jerome (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 1 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 2 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 3 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 4 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 5 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 6 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 7 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 8 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 9 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 10 of 51] (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 11 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 12 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 13 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 14 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 15 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 16 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 17 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 18 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 19 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 20 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 21 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 22 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 23 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 24 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 25 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 26 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 27 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 28 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 29 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 30 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 31 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 32 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 33 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 34 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 35 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 36 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 37 of 51] (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 38 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  See also Box 56, ff8
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 39 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 40 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 41 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 42 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 43 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 44 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 45 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 46 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 47 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 48 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 49 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 40 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Potofsky, Jacob [folder 51 of 51] (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Prager, Jack (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Previs, Joe (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Rabkin, Elias (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Ragnold, Fred (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Redden, Jackson (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Reiff, Hyman (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Reimbold, Wm. C. (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Reiss, Raymond (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Rheingold, Herman (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Ricciardelli, Vincent (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Richens, Sarah (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Rissman, Sidney (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Robinson, George (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Rocco, William (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Roitman, Irving (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Rosen, Chas. (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Rosen, Morris (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 1 of 23] (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 2 of 23] (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 3 of 23] (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 4 of 23] (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 5 of 23] (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 6 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  See also Box 56, ff9
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 7 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 8 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 9 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 10 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 11 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 12 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 13 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 14 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 15 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 16 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 17 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 18 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 19 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 20 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 21 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 22 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Rosenblum, Frank [folder 23 of 23] (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Rothbart, Isidore (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Rozner, Sarah (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Rudich, Philip (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Salerno, Carmen (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Salerno, Joseph [folder 1 of 4] (Box 12, Folder 23)
  See also Box 57, ff1
- Salerno, Joseph [folder 2 of 4] (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Salerno, Joseph [folder 3 of 4] (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Salerno, Joseph [folder 4 of 4] (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Samuel, Howard [folder 1 of 5] (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Samuel, Howard [folder 2 of 5] (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Samuel, Howard [folder 3 of 5] (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Samuel, Howard [folder 4 of 5] (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Samuel, Howard [folder 5 of 5] (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Samuel, Ralph (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Santora, Mami (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Schevetsky, N. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Schlossberg, Joseph [folder 1 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Schlossberg, Joseph [folder 2 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Schlossberg, Joseph [folder 3 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Schneid, Hyman (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Schneider, Mary (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Schubert, Joseph (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Schultheis, Ed (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Schultz, Loius (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Schwartz, Ernest (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Seibert, Henry (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Seitchik, Joseph (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Selm, Fred (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Senecal, J.M. (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Serafini, Henry (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Sheinkman, Jack [folder 1 of 6] (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Sheinkman, Jack [folder 2 of 6] (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Sheinkman, Jack [folder 3 of 6] (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Sheinkman, Jack [folder 4 of 6] (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Sheinkman, Jack [folder 5 of 6] (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Sheinkman, Jack [folder 6 of 6] (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Shoaff, James (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Shucker, Dr. George (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Siegel, Lewis (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Siegel, Nathann (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Silver, Jack (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Silver, Murray (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Silverman, Abe (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Simon, Louis [folder 1 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Simon, Louis [folder 2 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Simon, Louis [folder 3 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Skala, Stephen (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Slocum, John (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Slutsky, Samuel (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Smith, Samuel (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Sneed, Geneva (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Sobczak, John (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Sobieski, Frank (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Soden, Roy (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Spitzer, Morris (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Spivak, S. (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Steinberg, Dr. Martin (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Stone, M. Hedley (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Strebel, Gustave A. (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Sweeney, Annie Belle (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Swoboda, Pete (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Taylor, Dr. Geo. W. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Tomarken, Morris (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Toplitsky, Morris (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Troisi, Ralph (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Tupper, Rodney (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Wachtel, Mitchell (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Wallace, Anna (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Weiner, Jack (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Weinstein, Chas. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Weinstein, Chas. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Political Action Legislation, Testimony (see also Box 57, ff6) (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Weinstein, Florence (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Weinstein, Murray (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Wisgal, Isador (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Welker, Helen (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Wertheimer, Val (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Wyss, Harold (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Yannetti, Louis (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Zubal, Pete (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Zusman, Morris (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Zwickel, Aaron (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Banks and Banking ACWA First Opening of a Labor Bank in Chicago (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Banks and Banking ACWA Chicago (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York [folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York [folder 2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York, Ceremonies [folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York, Ceremonies [folder 2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York, Facilities [folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 8)
  See also Box 57 ff 2
- Banks and Banking ACWA New York, Facilities [folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Child Labor (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Community Aid (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Community Aid Charities (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Community Aid Foreign (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Community Aid Foreign, India (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Community Aid Foreign, Israel (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Community Aid Foreign, Italy (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Community Aid Foreign, Italy, Boys Town of [folder 1 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Community Aid Foreign, Italy, Boys Town of [folder 2 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Community Aid Foreign, Mexico (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Community Aid Health, City of Hope (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Community Aid Health, Blood Donation (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Convention, ACWA, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Convention, ACWA, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Convention, ACWA, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 1 of 2], 1940 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 1 of 2], 1940 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Convention, ACWA, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Convention, ACWA, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Convention, ACWA, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Convention, ACWA, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Convention, ACWA, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Convention, ACWA, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 1 of 2], 1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 2 of 2], 1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Convention, ACWA, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 1 of 2], 1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 2 of 2], 1960 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Convention, ACWA [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Duplicates (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Convention, ACWA, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Honored Guests and Speakers
- Convention, ACWA, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Honored Guests and Speakers, Singer Bowl
- Convention, ACWA, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Duplicates (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Convention, ACWA, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Convention, ACWA, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Convention, ACWA, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Convention, ACWA, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Convention, ACWA, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Convention, ACWA, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Convention, ACWA, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Special Session on Foreign Policy
- Convention, ACWA, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Day Care Centers Baltimore, Ceremonies (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Day Care Centers Baltimore, Facilities (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Day Care Centers Chambersburg, PA, Facilities (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Day Care Centers Chicago Joint Board (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Day Care Centers Hanover, PA, Facilities (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Day Care Centers Laundry Workers Joint Board, E. Harlem, NY, Ceremonies (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Day Care Centers Rochester Joint Board (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Day Care Centers Verona, VA, Ceremonies (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Day Care Centers Verona, VA, Facilities (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Duplicates (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Education Activities, Conferences (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Education Activities, Conferences, Staff (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Education Activities, Convention Displays (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Education Activities, Convention Programs, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Education Activities, Convention Programs, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Education Activities, Film and Paperback Library (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Education Activities, Activities, Institutes [folder 1 of 2] (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Education Activities, Activities, Institutes [folder 2 of 2] (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Education Activities, Radio Program, Town Hall (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Education Activities, Teaching (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Education Activities, Tours (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Education Activities, Visitors (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Education Activities, Visitors, Foreign [folder 1 of 2] (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Education Activities, Visitors, Foreign [folder 2 of 2] (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Education El Paso Joint Board, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Education General, Aid to Higher Education (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Education General, First Aid (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Education General, Tailoring (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Education Regional Activities (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Education Regional Activities, Baltimore Joint Board, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Education Regional Activities, Canada, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Education Regional Activities, Capitol District Joint Board, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Education Regional Activities, Cincinnati, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Education Regional Activities, Detroit, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Education Regional Activities, Kentuckiana Joint Board, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Education Regional Activities, Laundry Workers Joint Board, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Education Regional Activities, Los Angeles Joint Board, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Education Regional Activities, Midwest Regional Joint Board, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Education Regional Activities, Mississippi Joint Board (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Education Regional Activities, New England Regional Office, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Education Regional Activities, New York Joint Board, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Education Regional Activities, New York, Local 169, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Education Regional Activities, Pennsylvania Joint Board [folder 1 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Education Regional Activities, Pennsylvania Joint Board [folder 2 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Education Regional Activities, Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Education Regional Activities, Pittsburgh Joint Board, 1953-1969 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Education Regional Activities, Red Bank, NJ, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Education Regional Activities, Rochester Joint Board, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Education Regional Activities, Scranton Wilkes-Barre, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Education Regional Activities, Shirt and Leisurewear Joint Board, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Education Regional Activities, South 1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Education Regional Activities, Southeastern Clothing Regional Board, Palm Beach, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Education Regional Activities, Southwestern Regional Joint Board, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Education Regional Activities, Western organization Dept., 1948 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Education Schools, Alabama Southern School, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Education Schools, Eastern Summer School, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Education Schools, Georgia School, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Education Schools, Historical, through 1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Education Schools, Historical, Highlander Folk School (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Education Schools, Historical, Hudson Shore Labor (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Education Schools, Midwestern Summer School [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Education Schools, Midwestern Summer School [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Education Schools, Midwestern Summer School [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Education Schools, Mississippi School, 1958-1968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Education Schools, Mississippi School, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Education Schools, National Midwest School, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Education Schools, NC-SC-VA, East Shore School, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Education Schools, Southeastern Summer School, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  1968-1969, 1973
- Education Schools, Southern School, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Education Schools, Southwestern School, 1957-1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  1957-1965, 1970
- Educational Activities ACWA Labor Bookshelves (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Factories (Box 24, Folder 9)
  See also Box 57, ff2
- Factory Workers (Box 24, Folder 10)
  See also Box 57, ff3
- Reprints (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Negatives (Box 24, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board (Box 25, Folder 11)
  Reprints
- General Executive Board, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  Miscellaneous. and 1993
- Health Center Chicago (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Health Center Historical (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Health Center Israel, Jacob Potofsky Medical Center (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Health Center Laundry Workers, Ceremonies [folder 1 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Health Center Laundry Workers, Ceremonies [folder 1 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Health Center - Laundry Workers, Diagnosis and Treatment (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Health Center - Laundry Workers, Facilities (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Health Center - Laundry Workers, Offices and Personnel (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Health Center Mobile (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Health Center New York, Ceremonies (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Health Center Reprints (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Health Center New York, Diagnosis and Treatment [folder 1 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Health Center New York, Diagnosis and Treatment [folder 2 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Health Center New York, Diagnosis and Treatment [folder 3 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Health Center Reprint (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Health Center New York, Facilities [folder 1 of 2] (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Health Center New York, Facilities [folder 2 of 2] (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Health Center New York, Offices and Personnel (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Health Center New York, Rehabilitation (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Health Center Allentown, Reuben Block Health Fund Building (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Health Center Philadelphia, Ceremonies (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Health Center Philadelphia, Diagnosis and Treatment (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Health Center Philadelphia, Facilities (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Health Center Philadelphia, Offices and Personnel (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Health Services Women (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Hillman Foundation Educational Activities (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Hillman Foundation Executive Board (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Reprints (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Reprints (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Reprints (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Reprints (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Hillman Foundation Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Housing Chicago, Harper Square (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Housing Chicago, Kenwood Park, Ceremonies (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Reprints (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Housing Chicago, Kenwood Park, Ceremonies (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Housing General, United Housing Foundation (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Housing Chicago, United Housing Foundation, Co-op City (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Housing New York, Amalgamated Dwellings (Manhattan) (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Housing New York, Amalgamated Houses, Ceremonies (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Housing New York, Amalgamated Houses, Interior (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Housing New York, Amalgamated Houses, Exterior (Box 29, Folder 9)